https://www.northshoreroundup.com/privacy-policy/

Close HomeTicketsScheduleHotelFAQLinksCommitteeHistoryPast PostersContactPrivacy PolicyNorth Shore Round UpHomeTicketsScheduleHotelFAQLinksCommitteeHistoryPast PostersContactPrivacy Policy
Home » Privacy PolicyWho we areNorth Shore Round Up is https://www.northshoreroundup.com/newwww and all subdomains associated with north-shore-round-up.localYour privacy is very important to us.At North Shore Round Up we have a few fundamental principles that we follow.We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, or to protect our rights.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless it is required for the on-going operation of our site.What personal data we collect and why we collect itNorth Shore Round Up only collects data when it is entered by you on our contact form so that we can reply to request that you make of us. No other personally identifying data is collected.Contact formsOur contact form is used to transmit data to our GMail email address and is not directly stored on our website. Please see Google Privacy & Terms for more information about this.Our contact form also allows you to subscribe to our periodic email list that will be stored on our MailChimp account.  Please see MailChimp Privacy Policy for more information about this.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. North Shore Round Up uses cookies to help North Shore Round Up identify and track visitors and their usage of North Shore Round Up’s website.North Shore Round Up visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computer should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using North Shore Round Up’s website, with the drawback that certain features of the North Shore Round Up’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Cookies that are used on North Shore Round Up website (but are not limited to) are by Google Analytics.  Please see Google Privacy & Terms for more information about this.Embedded content from other websitesNorth Shore Round Up does not use any embedded content from other websites.AnalyticsNorth Shore Round Up uses Google Analytics to help improve the North Shore Round Up website. Most of this information is non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, general region the visitor is browsing from and the date and time of each visitor request. North Shore Round Up also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, names and email addresses through the use of contact forms.Please see Google Privacy & Terms for more information about this.Who we share your data withNorth Shore Round Up does not share your data with anyone.How long we retain your dataBy subscribing to our periodic newsletter you are allowing us to keep your name and email address. You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time.What rights you have over your dataYou have the right to ask for your data to be removed from our MailChimp email list at any time. This can be done by unsubscribing from our email list. This is an automated process and will be done as soon as the request is made.Where we send your dataEmail contacts including name and email address will be transmitted to our GMail email address.Newsletter subscription requests including your email address, first name and last initial will be transmitted to our MailChimp account. Additional informationHow we protect your dataNorth Shore Round Up strives to keep our website up to date applying all software patches as soon as they become available. North Shore Round Up uses secure passwords for any users administering the site and deactivates accounts when administrators leave the committee.What third parties we receive data fromNorth Shore Round Up does not receive any information from any third parties.What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataNorth Shore Round Up does not use any automated decision making processes. If you have any questions or concerns about North Shore Round Up’s website or privacy policy please contact usby emailing the North Shore Round Up Chair at nsruchair@gmail.comor by sending mail toNorth Shore Round UpP.O. Box 91086, WestVancouver, BC, CanadaV7V 3N3 Back to top
Copyright Text - Copyright ©
-
| North Shore Round Up,"We are going to know a new freedom and a new happiness". page 83 Big Book of AAThis site is provided by the North Shore Round Up Committee as a service to the community.It is not endorsed by Alcoholics Anonymous World Services, does not represent Alcoholics Anonymous as a whole.
Search:
